Dennis Roberts fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Dennis Roberts fonds
1967 - 1994
F-160
Q104814919
13 cm of textual records 132 sound recordings 25 buttons
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
PHYSICAL DESCRIPTION Fonds includes 134 audio cassettes and 4 audio tapes (reel-to-reel tapes).
Roberts, Dennis
Dennis Roberts was hired in August 1966 as SFU's first full-time Information Officer. In 1972, the Information Office became the University News Service, and Roberts served as its first director. He remained in this position until 1982, when he retired from the University. In addition to his regular duties, Dennis Roberts was in charge of the SFU Pipe and Drum Band for eight years. He was also well-known at SFU as a cartoonist and produced a series of cartoons for Christmas and other events that gently poked fun at various members of the SFU community.
published
Full
Revised
Title of the fonds is based on its provenance.
Fonds consists of records relating to Roberts's career at SFU. Includes correspondence, press releases, flyers, clippings, newsletters, publications, transcripts of speeches, notes, buttons, and cartoons and other artwork. Also includes a set of sound recordings made by Roberts while he was Director of the University News Service.
The materials were arranged by the archivist into two series, one for files and the other for audio recordings.
Artefacts; Sound recordings; Textual records; Communications
Dennis Roberts donated the fonds to the SFU Archives in 2001.
All accessions have been processed as of February 2006. No further accruals are expected.
See the inventory for Media and Public Relations, F-61.
There is one file relating to grievances that is restricted; the other files are open. Access to the original audio cassettes is restricted for preservation reasons. Consult the reference archivist for more information about accessing restricted material.
Series descriptions, file lists, and item lists are available. The hard-copy version of the finding aid (available in the Archives reading room) includes two appendices: a history of Information Services on Campus written by Roberts (Appendix B) and Roberts' detailed comments on the individual audio recordings found in Series 2 (Appendix C).
- Subject files, 1967 - 1994; F-160-1; 12 cm of textual records 25 buttons
  published
  Series consists of records relating to significant events in SFU's history as well as general biographical information on Dennis Roberts, his correspondence, and a selection of his writing including a lengthy history of the Alumni Association. Examples of significant events documented include the Admissions Protest in 1968 and the AUCE strike in 1979. Series contains correspondence, press releases, flyers, clippings, newsletters, publications, notes, transcripts of speeches, cartoons and other artwork. A file of ephemera contains humorous, unusual, or controversial publications and correspondence collected by Roberts during his years at SFU as well as a collection of SFU political and commemorative buttons.
  - Biographical information, 1970 - 1990; F-160-1-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 160-1)
    Textual records
    Open
  - Alumni Association history, 1968 - 1985; F-160-1-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 160-1)
    Simon Fraser University Alumni Association; Textual records
  - Articles, sketches and interviews by Dennis Roberts, 1967 - 1978; F-160-1-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 160-1)
  - Correspondence, 1968 - 1986; F-160-1-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 160-1)
  - AUCE strike, 1978 - 1979; F-160-1-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 160-1)
    Association of University and College Employees, Local 2; Textual records
  - Admissions protest, 1968; F-160-1-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 160-1)
  - CAUT - McTaggart-Cowan resignation, 1968; F-160-1-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 160-1)
    Canadian Association of University Teachers; McTaggart-Cowan, Patrick; Textual records
  - Fox, Terry, 1981; F-160-1-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 160-1)
    Fox, Terry; Textual records
  - Grievance proceedings, 1979; F-160-1-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 160-1)
    Restricted in whole
  - Oregon air crash, 1977; F-160-1-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 160-1)
  - PSA, 1968 - 1978; F-160-1-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 160-1)
    Department of Political Science, Sociology and Anthropology; Textual records
  - Release the hostages, please (Iran), 1980; F-160-1-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 160-1)
  - SFU Pipe and Drum band, 1980 - 1983; F-160-1-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 160-1)
    Simon Fraser University Pipe Band; Textual records
  - Sinnott, Ted, 1972 - 1981; F-160-1-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 160-1)
    Sinnott, Ted; Textual records
  - Templeton Secondary school incident, 1967; F-160-1-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 160-1)
    Templeton Secondary School; Textual records
  - University arts and architecture, 1974 - 1988; F-160-1-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 160-1)
  - University protests - general, 1968 - 1969; F-160-1-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 160-1)
  - Artwork and Christmas cartoons, 1969 - 1981; F-160-1-0-0-18
  - Ephemera, 1967 - 1994; F-160-1-0-0-19
  - Buttons, vol. 1, 1967 - 1987; F-160-1-0-0-20
  - Buttons, vol. 2, 1967 - 1987; F-160-1-0-0-21
- Audio recordings, 1968 - 1982; F-160-2; 132 sound recordings; Physical description: series includes 134 audio cassettes and 4 audio tapes (reel-to-reel).
  As Director of the University News Service, Dennis Roberts purchased a cassette recorder, which he took with him to meetings, interviews, and newsworthy events. Over the years, he captured the voices of students, staff, faculty and administrators. Although there are no transcripts for the recordings, many of them served as the basis for articles in Comment magazine, which contain additional information on the topic or individual interviewed. Topics include student protests; the dispute over the Political Science, Sociology and Anthopology (PSA) Department; interviews, speeches and news conferences with university Presidents, adminstrative officers, faculty members, staff and students.
  The recordings were donated to the Archivesin no "particular order" (in the words of the fonds creator). The original arrangement of the series left items in this found order. In September 2012, the archivist re-numbered the items and imposed a chronological arrangement. Note, however, that exact dates are not always known. See Appendix C for the found order.
  Department of Political Science, Sociology and Anthropology
  No further accruals are expected.
  Access to the sound recordings in analog format is restricted for preservation reasons due to the age and fragility of the medium (audio cassette). The Archives will provide accessonly through digitization. As of September 2012, no access copies have been made. Consult with the reference archivist for more information about accessing the recordings.
  Appendix C in the hardcopy version of the finding aid contains additional comments about the audio recordings made by Roberts (available in the Archives Reading Room).
  - Evening course in protests, [196-?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3355)
    A - Evening course in protests (4 min. ? version)
    Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-34.1 orig., F-160-item34.
  - Senate Undergrad Admissions committee meeting to discuss student demands, [1968?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-2 (Audio cassette OBJ-3356)
    A - Senate Undergrad Admissions committee meeting to discuss student demands
    Senate Undergraduate Admissions Board; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-4.1 orig., F-160-item4.
  - Union negotiation; removal of students, [1968?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-3 (Audio cassette OBJ-3357)
    A- Suart / Union Negotiations. // chanting // vote.
    B - "Way It Is' - Strand on police removal of students // news
    Suart, George; Strand, Kenneth; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-26.1 orig., F-160-item26.
  - Dr. Kenneth Strand addresses university community on the Mall after the occupation, 1968; F-160-2-0-0-0-5 (Audio cassette OBJ-3359)
    A, B - Dr. Kenneth Strand addresses university community on the Mall after the occupation
    Strand, Kenneth; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-23.1 orig., F-160-item23.
  - Strand address, 8 September 1968; F-160-2-0-0-0-7 (Audio cassette OBJ-3361)
    A - Strand Address
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-27.1 orig., F-160-item27.
  - Students in Administration Buiding re: Admissions Policy, 20 November 1968; F-160-2-0-0-0-8 (Audio cassette OBJ-3362)
    A, B - Evans and Strand - students in Admin. Bldg. Re Admissions Policy
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-25.1 orig., F-160-item25.
  - Administration building occupaton, 23 November 1968; F-160-2-0-0-0-9 (Audio cassette OBJ-3363)
    A - End of Admin. Bldg. Occupation (taped by Science Dean L. Funt), police movements, crowd, music, chanting. B - Discussion re shows / Strand News Conference on police call-in
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-20.1 orig., F-160-item20.
  - Charges against students, 24 November 1968; F-160-2-0-0-0-10 (Audio cassette OBJ-3364)
    A, B - Suart, Sullivan, etc. re News Conference - charges against students
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-21.1 orig., F-160-item21.
  - Strand news conference, 11 December 1968; F-160-2-0-0-0-12 (Audio cassette OBJ-3365)
    A - Strand News Conference. B- cont'd // Strand statement re committee recommendations
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-22.1 orig., F-160-item22.
  - PSA dispute, [1969?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-13 (Audio cassette OBJ-3366)
    A - R. Lester, BOG, Chair re Aberle firing // Wasserman comment // Webster / Lester.
    B - Lester / Webster cont'd // ground rules
    Lester, Richard E.; Wasserman, Jack; Webster, Jack; Aberle, Kathleen; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-3.1.orig., F-160-item3.
  - Palmer decision, [1969?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-14 (Audio cassette OBJ-3367)
    A, B - Palmer decision // news conf. with 1 of dismissed profs. // Strand stmnt re Palmer decision // Strand discussion re action
    Strand, Kenneth; Palmer, Earl E.; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-5. 1 orig., F-160-item5.
  - Briemberg appeal hearings, [1969?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-15 (Audio cassette OBJ-3368)
    A - Briemberg appeal hearings - second session
    Briemberg, Mordecai; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-8. 1 orig., F-160-item8.
  - PSA 7 seeking reinstatement, [1969?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-16 (Audio cassette OBJ-3369)
    A - Jack Webster / Mordicai Briemberg.
    B - PSA 7 seeking reinstatement.
    Briemberg, Mordecai; Webster, Jack; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-15.1 orig., F-160-item15.
  - Chanting "On Strike, Shut it Down" to Strand, [1969?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-17 (Audio cassette OBJ-3370)
    A, B - Chanting "On Strike, Shut it Down" to Strand
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-16.1 orig., F-160-item16.
  - Briemberg news conference; interview with SFU first Academic Planner, Ron Baker, [1969?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-18 (Audio cassette OBJ-3371)
    A - Briemberg News Conference.
    B - Interview with SFU first Academic Planner, Ron Baker.
    Briemberg, Mordecai; Baker, Ron; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-24.1 orig., F-160-item24.
  - PSA dispute, February 1969; F-160-2-0-0-0-20 (Audio cassette OBJ-3373)
    A - Prof. Briemberg / P.S.A. statement to counter Sun allegations re Dept. / Press Conference
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-7. 1 orig., F-160-item7.
  - PSA strike, 11 September 1969; F-160-2-0-0-0-22 (Audio cassette OBJ-3375)
    A, B - Wasserman / Strand - Charges of purge, PSA strike, police on Campus
    Wasserman, Jack; Strand, Kenneth; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-18.1 orig., F-160-item18.
  - PSA strike; Wasserman: dogs, hitchhiker, 30 September 1969; F-160-2-0-0-0-23 (Audio cassette OBJ-3376)
    A - Webster / Sullivan - PSA Strike. B - cont'd // Wasserman - Dogs, hitchhiker
    Wasserman, Jack; Webster, Jack; Sullivan, Dale; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-17.1 orig., F-160-item17.
  - PSA trusteeship and strike, October 1969; F-160-2-0-0-0-25 (Audio cassette OBJ-3377)
    A - Webster / Briemberg, // News.
    B - Dale Sullivan, Dean of Arts, announcement re PSA trusteeship and strike // Ken Strand, Acting President, statement re PSA dismissals // more student protests / demos re PSA strike
    Webster, Jack; Briemberg, Mordecai; Strand, Kenneth; Sullivan, Dale; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-1.1 orig., F-160-item1.
  - Joint Faculty meeting, 9 October 1969; F-160-2-0-0-0-26 (Audio cassette OBJ-3378)
    A - Joint Faculty meeting (students asked to leave / shouting)
    Joint Faculty; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-10.1 orig., F-160-item10.
  - "Now There is a Mountain" - CBC semi-documentary by Peter Hay, 22 October 1969; F-160-2-0-0-0-27 (Audio cassette OBJ-3379)
    A - "Now There is a Mountain" - CBC semi-documentary by Peter Hay
    Canadian Broadcasting Corporation; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-9. 1 orig., F-160-item9.
  - Prudence Wheeldon (PSA) appeal, 24 November 1969; F-160-2-0-0-0-28 (Audio cassette OBJ-3380)
    A, B - Prudence Wheeldon, PSA Prof. Appeal against suspension
    Wheeldon, Prudence; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-11.1 orig., F-160-item11.
  - Wheeldon appeal, Feldhamer appeal, 24 November 1969; F-160-2-0-0-0-29 (Audio cassette OBJ-3381)
    A - Wheeldon appeal cont'd // Feldhamer appeal.
    B - Feldhamer appeal.
    Wheeldon, Prudence; Feldhammer, Louis; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-12.1 orig., F-160-item12.
  - Feldhamer appeal, Leggett appeal; bagpipes, 24 November 1969; F-160-2-0-0-0-30 (Audio cassette OBJ-3382)
    A - Feldhamer appeal cont'd.
    B - Feldhamer appeal cont'd // Bagpipes // Leggatt appeal
    Feldhammer, Louis; Leggett, John C.; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-13.1 orig., F-160-item13.
  - Spencer Horrell memorial service, [197-?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-31 (Audio cassette OBJ-3383)
    A - Spencer Horrell Memorial Service
    Spencer Horrell; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-67.1 orig., F-160-item67.
  - Ed Larson Memorial Service; release US hostages in Iran campaign, [197-?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-32 (Audio cassette OBJ-3384)
    A - Ed Larson Memorial Service.
    B - Release US hostages in Iran campaign.
    Ed Larson; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-69.1 orig., F-160-item69.
  - Cunningham, Wasserman, Webster, Gardom, 14 February [1970?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-51 (Audio cassette OBJ-3402)
    A - Dr. Allen Cunningham to Wasserman / Webster / Gardom re SFU situation.
    B - Webster re Free school, threats
    Cunningham, Allan B.; Wasserman, Jack; Webster, Jack; Garde Gardom; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-14.1 orig., F-160-item14.
  - PSA trusteeship, August 1970; F-160-2-0-0-0-52 (Audio cassette OBJ-3403)
    A - Dean of Arts Balier (?) re student parity and PSA trusteeship.
    B - Strand re Palmer dec. - new committee
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-2.1 orig., F-160-item2.
  - CAUT censure, labour relations and unions, 14 May 1971; F-160-2-0-0-0-57 (Audio cassette OBJ-3408)
    A, B - Strand statement and Press Conference re CAUT Censure // Eng. Diplomat // Labour Relations and Unions
    Strand, Kenneth; Canadian Association of University Teachers; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-19.1 orig., F-160-item19.
  - Dismissals, academic freedom; Marine Station, Bamfield, July–August 1971; F-160-2-0-0-0-58 (Audio cassette OBJ-3409)
    A - Lester statement on Wyland // Strand statement on dismissals // Pat Burns interviews Stanley Cooperman, academic or political freedom in Universities.
    B - cont'd // Marine Station, Bamfield, with Glen Geen.
    Lester, Richard E.; Geen, Glen H.; Pat Burns; Cooperman, Stanley; Western Canadian Universities Marine Biological Station; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-6. 1 orig., F-160-item6.
  - Mennell / Vergin interview; Suart interview re: trades strike, 1972; F-160-2-0-0-0-59 (Audio cassette OBJ-3410)
    A - Ken Mennell interviews swimming champion Vergin.
    B - VP Admin George Suart interview after Trades strike.
    Mennell, Ken; Suart, George; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-70.1 orig., F-160-item70.
  - Jack Ramsey, Robert Wilder deportation, Graham Dawson fundraising, 20 March 1972; F-160-2-0-0-0-62 (Audio cassette OBJ-3412)
    A - Jack Ramsey (Sun) // Robert wilder deportation // Graham Dawson - Fundraising
    Jack Ramsey; Graham Dawson; Robert Wilder; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-31.1 orig., F-160-item31.
  - Harold Robbins and Arthur Hailey speeches; Roberts / Hailey interview, 13 November 1972; F-160-2-0-0-0-63 (Audio cassette OBJ-3413)
    A - Speeches by novelists Harold Robbins and Arthur Hailey in Detroit during PR convention.
    B - Interview with Arthur Hailey by Dennis Roberts, (Comment).
    Hailey, Arthur; Harold Robbins; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-72.1 orig., F-160-item72.
  - Strand: retreat, public policy, 1–2 December 1972; F-160-2-0-0-0-64 (Audio cassette OBJ-3414)
    A - Retreat - Strand.
    B - Public Policy - Strand.
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-28.1 orig., F-160-item28.
  - Strand - resignation announcement, 1973; F-160-2-0-0-0-65 (Audio cassette OBJ-3415)
    A - Strand - resignation announcement
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-32.1 orig., F-160-item32.
  - Roberts, CKNW re: Watergate, "Land of Strand", Roger Welch of SFSS, 9 November 1973, 1 May 1974; F-160-2-0-0-0-68 (Audio cassette OBJ-3418)
    A - Stan Roberts, CKNW "Investigators" re Watergate. B - "Land of Strand" slide show // Roger Welch of SFSS
    CKNW Radio; Roberts, Stanley; Roger Welch; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-33.1 orig., F-160-item33.
  - Strand, Webster, McEachern, Universities Task Force, 1974; F-160-2-0-0-0-69 (Audio cassette OBJ-3419)
    A - Webster / Strand.
    B - cont'd // Webster / John McEachen of Universities Task Force.
    Webster, Jack; Strand, Kenneth; John McEachern; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-29.1 orig., F-160-item29.
  - Ted Sinnott's 80th birthday, 1 February 1974; F-160-2-0-0-0-72 (Audio cassette OBJ-3422, Audio cassette OBJ-3423)
    A - Ted Sinnott's 80th birthday party on Mall.
    B - News hour report on Ted (SFU Beloved Janitor) and his party.
    Sinnott, Ted; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-64.1 orig., F-160-item64.
  - Gzowski / Jewett interview; Strand on government appropriations, 1 April 1974; F-160-2-0-0-0-73 (Audio cassette OBJ-3424)
    A - CBC Gzowksi / Jewett interview.
    B - Government appropriations - Ken Strand statement.
    Gzowski, Peter; Jewett, Pauline; Canadian Broadcasting Corporation; Strand, Kenneth; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-49.1 orig., F-160-item49.
  - SFU Pipes and Drums award night, 17 April 1974; F-160-2-0-0-0-74 (Audio cassette OBJ-3425)
    A, B - SFU Pipes and Drums award night
    Simon Fraser University Pipe Band; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-61.1 orig., F-160-item61.
  - Jewett, Bannerman, Jacques Khouri, 11 September 1974; F-160-2-0-0-0-75 (Audio cassette OBJ-3426)
    A, B - Jewett // Bannerman / Jacques Khouri - on The story of her life, goals, role of University (CKNW)
    Jewett, Pauline; Jacques Khouri; Bannerman, Gary; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-47.1 orig., F-160-item47.
  - Jewett welcome - building plans, 12 September 1974; F-160-2-0-0-0-76 (Audio cassette OBJ-3427)
    A - Jewett welcome - building plans
    Jewett, Pauline; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-36.1 orig., F-160-item36.
  - Captain Canada mini-bike jump over AQ pool; Province Empty Stocking Fund; CBC Allan Garr Show, CBC Morning Show; Ted McWhinney, 21 November 1974; F-160-2-0-0-0-77 (Audio cassette OBJ-3428)
    A - "Captain Canada" Mini-bike jump over the AQ pool - fund raiser for Province Empty Stocking Fund // Allan Garr Show, CBC // CBC Morning Show.
    B - Prof. Ted McWhinney interview
    Garr, Alan; Canadian Broadcasting Corporation; McWhinney, Edward; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-62.1 orig., F-160-item62.
  - Budget, Senate and Strand on Budget Committee, 1974; F-160-2-0-0-0-78 (Audio cassette OBJ-3429)
    A - Webster / Brian Wilson - Budgets.
    B - cont'd // Senate and Strand on Budget Committee.
    Webster, Jack; Strand, Kenneth; Wilson, Brian G.; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-30.1 orig., F-160-item30.
  - Roberts / Jewett interview, Paul Cote announcing appointment of new President, 1974; F-160-2-0-0-0-79 (Audio cassette OBJ-3430)
    A - Roberts / Jewett interview.
    B - Paul Cote announcing appointment of new President
    Jewett, Pauline; Roberts, Dennis; Coté, Paul T.; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-35.1 orig., F-160-item35.
  - Brian Sketchley, SFU Parachute Club, official welcome to Jewett, 1974; F-160-2-0-0-0-80 (Audio cassette OBJ-3431)
    A - Brian Sketchley, SFU Parachute Club - Official welcome to Jewett
    Jewett, Pauline; Sketchley, Brian; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-37.1 orig., F-160-item37.
  - Jewett welcome, Goon Show "The Missing Tapes", 1974; F-160-2-0-0-0-81 (Audio cassette OBJ-3432)
    A - Radio report of Jewett welcome.
    B - Goon Show "The Missing Tapes".
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-38.1 orig., F-160-item38.
  - Webster/ Jewett re appointment to SFU, 1974; F-160-2-0-0-0-82 (Audio cassette OBJ-3433, Audio cassette OBJ-3434)
    A, B - Webster/ Jewett re appointment to SFU.
    Webster, Jack; Jewett, Pauline; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-39.1 orig., C-160-2-0-40.1 orig., F-160-item39, F-160-item40.
  - Denise Holst interview, 1974; F-160-2-0-0-0-83
    A, B - Interview with Denise Holst, a courageous quadriplegic who became an SFU tour guide (Comment magazine)
    Denise Holst; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-76.1 orig., F-160-item76.